gomastercard.com.au 2008-12-17

# privacy_and_security

**Who has provided this site**   
The informational pages, apply online and service Centre functions   
are maintained and hosted by GE Capital Finance Australia (ABN 42   
008 583 588) trading as GE Money. Any information you submit at this   
site will be sent directly to GE Money. GE Money is the credit provider   
for GO MasterCard.

GE Money are committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal   
information.

We take the privacy and security of your transactions seriously. Our   
site contains links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that   
share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not   
responsible for the privacy practices or the content (or accuracy of   
content) of other web sites to which you provide your personal   
information. If you have any questions about this, or the content or   
practices of this web site, you can contact 

Customer Care.

 **Your personal information on the web  
**

We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless   
you apply for a card online or register for access to the online Service   
Centre. If you would like to know more about our privacy practices   
concerning your personal information, please refer to the Important   
Privacy Notices of GE Money and their related bodies. [http://www.gemoney.com.au/en/privacy_policy.html](http://www.gemoney.com.au/en/privacy_policy.html)

 **Applying for a card on the web  
**

When you apply for a GO MasterCard online, the Important Privacy   
Notices provide detailed information about the collection, use and   
disclosure of your personal information and informs you of other   
matters of which the Privacy Act requires us to make you aware. You   
should read these carefully. **Online Service Centre  
** When you register for access to the online Service Centre, the   
information collected is compared with the details we already have   
stored, such as your name, date of birth and GO MasterCard card   
number, which we have previously collected from you so we can verify   
that you are the person seeking access to your personal information. If   
you do not provide the information requested, you will not be able to   
access the online Service Centre.

When you submit feedback or questions via email, it is very important   
that you do not disclose any details that could be used by others to   
gain access to your account. This includes private details such as your   
username, password or GO MasterCard number.  
To ensure we properly protect your privacy and for security reasons,   
we cannot respond to your query via email if the answer would   
disclose account information personal to you. You will be directed to   
contact us using another method if this occurs.

 **Cookies  
** A cookie is a tiny element of data that a web site can send to your   
browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive, so you can be   
recognised when you return.

You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.  
Cookies are used on this web site to monitor the traffic to the site.   
They are used to count the number of visitors to each page and to   
track the path each visitor takes to navigate this web site, but no   
personal information about you is collected during this process.  
The online Service Centre uses cookies as part of the registration   
process. They are used to store the username while the customer is   
using the Service Centre and to track the number of times the user   
has tried to log in during a single visit. They are not used for any other   
purpose on this site.

 **Web site security  
** We use high security levels for our online Service Centre and when   
you apply for a GO MasterCard online. We use security levels which   
are standard for internet banking and large scale e-commerce sites.   
You can check the security level of a web page by clicking on your   
internet browser's padlock or key icon.

Encryption is the standard way of protecting your information as it is   
transmitted between you and us. This involves converting the   
information into an unreadable code using a "key" (and also de-coding   
it using this "key"). The longer the key, the more difficult it is for others   
to break the encrypted code.

To access the online Service Centre or to apply for a GO MasterCard   
online, your browser needs to be enabled to access these secure   
sites.
